你上次见他是什么时候
So, when did you see him last?
上周
Last week.
他跟你说我帮他在夜店找到工作了吗
Did he, uh, tell you I got him a job at the club?
嗯  他说了
Yeah, he mentioned that.
- 你钱还够用吗 - 我们还好
-How are you off for money? -Yeah, we're ok.
需要什么  跟我说就行
If you need anything, you just let me know.
我们会没事的  不过谢了
-Yeah, we'll be ok, but thanks. -Mmm.
天啊
Jesus.
我不知道我要干嘛
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
就是
I mean...
我都还没跟麦迪说过
I haven't mentioned anything to maddy yet.
你不会要跟她说他那个
you're not gonna tell her that he, um...
就是你懂的
You know...
- 她都7岁了  - 对啊
-She's 7. -Ok. Right.
没毛病
Fair enough.
我就说是车祸好了
I'll just...Say it was an accident.
好吧
Yeah.
真是个混蛋啊
What a fucking dickhead.
先生
中间人
第2季
第9集
翻译： 岛岛
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
翻译： Pretender
- 好了  - 你想看什么
-alright. -What do you wanna see?
翻译：文睿菌
不知道  你们想看什么
I don't know. What do you guys wanna see?
校对： 岛岛
- 那个  - 那个不错
-That. -Yeah, that looks good.
特效： 转轮手枪
- 温妮时来运转  - 嗯
-'winnie's big break'. -Yeah.
时间轴： 麦斯
荒原好不好
What about 'outlanding'?
- 不  - 那是纪录片啊
-No. -That's a documentary.
不  是电影啊
Ray: No, it's a movie.
不是的  你看  根据真实故事改编
No, look - 'based on true story'.
这也不代表是纪录片啊
Yeah, it doesn't mean it's a doco, though.
就是啊
Yeah!
不是  就说明是真实故事改编啊
No, just means it's based on a true story.
不  我们要看那个
No, we wanna watch that one.
- 温妮时来运转  - 嗯
-'winnie's big break'? -Yeah!
好无聊啊那个
That's boring!
不  你想看的才无聊  你看啊
No, that's way lamer. Look at it.
这样  谁想看温妮时来运转
Who wants to see 'winnie's big break'?
- 二比一啊  - 我无所谓啊
-Outvoted! -I don't care.
- 嘘 - 干啥
-shh! -What?
- 别扔了  - 咋了
-Stop! -What?
我好无聊
I'm bored.
我也是
Me too.
那就来帮我挑袜子啊
Help me find some socks, then.
袜子  无聊
Socks? Boring!
- 袜子很重要的  - 为什么
-Socks are important. -Why?
穿了袜子脚就不臭啊
Well, they stop your feet from smelling.
你脚本来就臭啊
Your feet stink anyway.
是的  雷叔叔  你脚可臭了
Yeah, uncle ray, your feet stink!
- 是吗 -  臭晕我
-Ray: Do they? -They pong.
对啊
Yeah!
你臭臭
You pong.
你这说的都啥玩意啊
Brittany: That doesn't even make any sense.
你说的才啥玩意呢
Well, you don't make any sense.
我们能去看自行车嘛  爸爸
Can we go look at the bikes, dad?
对啊
Maddy: Yeah!
- 自行车在哪 - 那边
-Where's the bikes? -Over there.
好不好呀
Please?!
好吧
Ray: Alright.
别跑远了
Don't go anywhere else.
- 麦迪  - 嗯
-Hey, maddy? -Yeah?
自己选个生日礼物吧
Pick something out for your birthday.
- 好  - 我也能选个东西吗  爸爸
-Ok! -Can I get something, dad?
你要过生日了吗
Is it your birthday?
- 没啊  - 那你还问
-No. -Well...
我能要这个吗  爸爸
can I get this, dad?
不行
Nuh.
- 好不好嘛  - 不行  放回去
-Please? -No. Put it back.
- 你都不给我买东西  - 我天天给你买东西好吗
-You never buy me anything. -I buy you stuff all the time.
- 那给我买啊  - 不行啊
-So buy me this! -No.
为什么啊
Why?
因为如果你要啥我给你买啥
'cause if I do buy you everything you want,
你就会成为一个被宠坏的小混蛋
you're gonna grow up to be a spoiled brat.
我都不知道这是啥意思
I don't even know what that is.
被宠坏的小混蛋就是什么都能得到的小孩
A spoiled brat is a person who gets everything they want
然后就很弱鸡  事儿很多  各种抱怨
and they're weak and... And whingey and whiny.
你以后想变成这样吗
Is that what you wanna be when you grow up?
- 不  - 那就放回去
-No. -Come on. Put it back.
- 麦迪呢  - 我不知道
-Where's maddy? -Um, I don't know.
她骑到别的地方去了
She rode off somewhere.
- 骑到哪里去了  - 那边吧
-Rode off where? -Uh, around there.
- 我去那边看看  - 不  你别离开我旁边
-I'll go look over here. -No, you stay with me, please.
- 那是她骑的车子吗 -  好像是
-Is that the bike she was on? -I think so.
麦迪
Brittany: Maddy?
Maddy!
卧槽了
for fuck's sake.
- 你怎么样啊  亲 - 你好
-how you goin', love? -Hello.
- 我女儿丢了  - 叫什么
-I've lost my daughter. -Oh, what's her name?
- 麦迪  - 好  我发广播找找
-Maddy. -Ok. I'll get on the p.A.
好的
Alright.
麦迪  请到前台来
Maddy, can you please come to the front counter?
- 呆在这  - 麦迪请来前台
-Just stay here. -Maddy to the front counter.
- - 有消息吗  - 还没有
-How'd you go, love? -Oh, nothing yet.
- 你在哪丢的她  - 就在左边
-Where did you lose her? -Uh, just down on the left.
你找过试衣间了吗
Have you checked the changing rooms?
- 在哪里  - 来  我带你去
-Whereabouts are they? -Oh, I'll show you. Come on.
这边
This way.
- 你的鞋很好看啊 -  谢谢
-I like your sneakers! -Brittany: Thanks.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
你看这一溜  我看这边
You take that side and I'll take this side.
你们这里有监控的吗
Have you got cctv cameras, have you?
- 有 - 这些都会看的吧
-Yeah. -You monitor those, do you?
- 对  在后面  - 好的
-Yeah, out the back. -Alright.
我们能去看一下吗
Can we go and have a look at them?
- 好  来吧 -  走
-Sure. Come with me. -Come on.
- 韦恩 - 对吧
-Wayne? - how's this, right?
他根本不会弄  然后把
He never got the feature and then...
- 韦恩  - 然后就把他踢出去了
-Wayne. -And they kicked him out!
干什么啊
what the fuck?!
给我看看之前十分钟的监控
The last 10 minutes, mate. I wanna see your footage, ok?
- 在哪里来着  - 水上运动区
-Where were we, love? -Uh, the water sports section.
水上运动区  十分钟之前的监控
Ray: Water sports section, last 10 minutes.
韦恩  赶紧的  他小孩丢了
Wayne, please. His kid's missing.
- 继续  - 这就是10分钟前的了
-Ray: Keep going. -Well, that's 10 minutes.
要停了我会说  继续放
Ok, I'll let you know, mate. Keep going.
好  听  你看
Ok. Stop it there. Right?
放大这个人
Zoom in on the guy.
好
Ok.
- 我要报警吗  - 不用
-Should I call the police? -Nuh.
我靠了
-Wayne: Jesus christ! -Hey...
雷大哥
raymondo.
你听我说  哥们
Need you to listen, mate, alright?
德克的小孩被人带走了  在购物中心
Dirk's kid's been grabbed, ok? From a shopping centre.
我拿到这人照片了
I got a photo of the guy.
我现在发给你
I'm gonna send that to you now, ok?
好的  需要我干什么
Yeah, ok, mate. What do you need?
你能查一下马里克维尔区
You reckon you can get a list
周围所有的性犯罪者吗
of all the sex offenders around the marrickville area?
可以  有个警察可以问
Yeah, yeah. I got a cop I can reach out to.
查到了尽快发给你  还有什么事
I'll get that asap and get it to you. Anything else?
尽你所能吧  哥们
Uh, look, anything you can do, mate.
需要你了联系你
I'm gonna need your help, ok?
- 没问题  - 好的
-Freddy: Yep. I'm on it. -Sweet.
还看不了
fuck.
- 喂  - 喂  我需要你
-yeah, mate? -Mate, I need your help.
我朋友的孩子在马里克维尔区
Mate of mine's kid's been grabbed
的购物中心被人带走了
from a shopping centre in marrickville.
- 什么  - 对  她被人拐走了
-What? -Yeah, she got grabbed.
有人拐走了她  我有那个人的照片
Somebody grabbed her, ok? I got a photo of the guy, alright?
我现在把照片发给你  好吧
I'm gonna send that to you now, alright?
- 行  - 好的  伙计
-Ok. -Great, mate. Ok.
我需要你快点出去
And need you to get out there,
找到那个混蛋  好吗
try to track this prick down, alright?
知道了  别担心  我马上去
Yeah, don't worry. I'm on it.
好吧  谢谢你伙计
Ok. Thanks, mate.
把你的安全带系上  布里特妮
Put your belt on, brit.
- 请系上安全带  - 我想要妈妈
-Seatbelt, please. -I want mum.
听着  我得找到麦迪  好吗
Look, I gotta find maddy, alright?
请系上安全带  好吗
Please put your belt on, ok?
快点  快点
Come on, come on!
- 嘿  - 妈妈
-hey! -Mum...
嘘  嘘  没事了
Shh. Shh, it's ok.
- 本尼  你好  - 哦 盖斯
-zdravstvujtye, benny. -Oh, gaz.
请坐
Yeah, please.
请坐请坐
Please, please.
- 坐吧  - 你好
-Take a seat. -Zdravstvujtye.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
你知道些什么
What do you know?
我放出话了
So, I put word out.
找了些人去问了
Spoke to some people.
我有个伙伴认识这个人
One of my associates knows this guy
他提过有个以前
who told story about this fellow
他去买过大麻的人
who he was buying weed from.
他说他们交易的时候
He said when they went to do deal,
那个人问他
this guy, he says,
你要看看我的玩具吗
"you want to see my toys?"
- 玩具  - 玩具
-toys? -Toys.
操
Fuckin' hell.
知道他的名字吗
Got a name for this guy?
皮吉
Pidgy.
- 皮吉  - 皮吉  听起来像鸽子
-Pidgy? -Pidgy, like pigeon.
皮吉  好
Pidgy. Right.
- 她在哪  - 什么
-Where is she? -What?
她在哪
where is she?
皮吉
pidgy?
是  你是谁
Yeah. Who are you?
我是哈桑的一个朋友  我需要问你点事
I'm a friend of hassan's. I just need some information.
行  进来吧
Alright. Come in.
- 我发誓  伙计  - 5 4
-I swear to god, mate... -Five. Four.
- 我什么都没干  - 3 2
-I haven't done anything! -Three. Two.
- 我什么都不知道啊  - 1
-I don't know anything! -One.
- 求你了  - 你今天早上在哪
-Please! -Where were you this morning?
- 你今天早上在哪  - 我一直在家没出门
-Where were you this morning?! -I haven't left the house.
你几个月前从一个家伙那里买大麻了吗
Did you buy some weed off a bloke couple of months ago
他当时跟你说他有些玩具可以卖给你
who said he had some 'toys' he wanted to sell you?
伙计  你得跟我说实话  明白吗
Mate, you just need to be honest with me now, alright?
如果你说实话  什么事都没有
If you're straight with me, we got nothing to worry about.
但如果你不说  那你就他妈的有麻烦了  明白吗
But if you're not, then we've got a fucking problem, ok?
那个有玩具的家伙是谁
Who's this bloke with the 'toys'?
这个人是谁
Who's this guy?
- 他是谁  - 我不知道
-Who is it? -I don't know.
我以前从来没见过他  对不起  我不知道啊
I've never seen that guy before. I'm sorry, I don't know.
对不起
I'm sorry.
是  我是在恩摩尔从一个人手里买了好几公斤的大麻
Yeah, I bought a couple of kilos off a bloke in enmore.
从他那买了好几个月了
Been buying off him for a couple of months.
有一天  他问我  你想要玩具吗
One day, he says do I wanna buy some toys?
然后我说  好啊  当然
And I said, "yeah, sure."
但是  我不知道
but...I didn't know.
我以为他说的玩具是枪或者什么的
Thought he must be talking about guns or something.
总之  我们走进他的地下室
Anyway, we go down in this basement.
那有个隐藏的房间  在一个橱柜后面
There's a concealed room. It's behind a cupboard, right?
门上一把又大又旧的锁
Big old lock on the door.
我们打开了走了进去
We open it, we go in.
看到好多孩子  就在那
There was these kids. Just there.
税务会计
-亲爱的 - 嗯
-Babe! -Yeah?
卫生纸都哪去了
Where's all the dunny paper?
用完了吗
Are we out?
洗手间里一卷都没有了
There's none in the bathroom.
那就是用完了呗
Must be out then.
上周那里放着  差不多10卷呢
Well, there was, like, 10 rolls in there last week.
是啊
Yep.
就是一天用掉一卷
So, like, that's a roll a day.
对头
Yeah.
怎么的  你一天拉10次吗
What, are you, like, shitting 10 times a day or something?
没有
No.
嘿  听着  我不是在怪你
Hey, look, I'm not having a go at ya,
我只是想搞明白你用那么多卫生纸干什么
I'm just trying to understand why you need so much of it.
好吧  是这么回事
Ok, here's how it goes.
- 我尿完要擦一下  对吗  - 对
-I pee, I wipe, ok? -Yeah.
然后我用私处湿巾
Ok, then I use my intimate wipes.
私处湿巾
Your intimate wipes?
对  然后我再拿点卫生纸  再擦干
Yes. Then I grab some more toilet paper and I wipe again.
为什么你要再擦一次呢
Why do you wipe again?
因为我的私处湿巾是湿的
Because my intimate wipes are wet.
我不能下面湿着就出去乱逛  是不是
I can't be walking round all wet down there, can I?
好吧  那你需要多少
Ok, so how much...
那  你用卫生纸擦干自己的时候
Like, when you grab the toilet paper to dry yourself,
你一般用几截
how many squares are we talking?
我不按截用  我整卷的用
I don't go by squares. I scrunch.
行吧  你为什么不撕下一截然后再折一下
Alright. Why don't you just take one square or fold...
因为那样我会把尿蹭手上啊  所以我整卷的用
Because I'll get pee on my hands. That's why I scrunch.
你也不想让我用沾了尿的手碰你对不对
You don't want me touching you with pee on my hands, do ya?
你尿完都不洗手吗
Don't you wash your hands afterwards?
我洗手  不好意思
Yes, I do wash my hands! I'm sorry.
你供不起我一天一卷卫生纸吗
Can you not afford one roll of toilet paper a day?
嘿  我可以给你买一货车卫生纸
Hey, I can buy a truckload of the stuff.
那你还叽叽歪歪个屁啊
Then why are you being such a dick?
我不是跟你叽歪  我只是
I'm not being a dick. I'm just, like...
嘿  伙计
hey, mate.
- 需要跟你谈谈  - 谈什么
-Need to talk to you. -What about?
需要跟你女婿谈谈
Wanna talk to your son-in-law.
- 纳西尔  谈什么  - 德克的孩子
-Nasir? About what? -Dirk's kid.
- 德克的孩子  - 对
-Dirk's kid? -Yeah.
伙计  我可以现在就告诉你
Mate, I can tell you right now
他跟那事没关系
he's got nothing to do with that.
- 我们走伙计  - 什么
-Let's go, mate. -What?
- 走  快点  - 去哪
-Let's go. Come on. -Go where?
- 快点  伙计  我们走了  - 雷  雷
-Come on. We're going, mate. -Ray! Ray.
- 我还有事呢  - 我才不管你有事没事呢
-I've got shit to do. -I don't give a fuck.
他是个会计
He's an accountant.
天啊  雷
jesus christ, ray!
伙计  一大家子人呢  你别太过分了好吗
now, mate, this is family here, so just take it easy, ok?
我来说  行吗
Let me do the talking, ok?
行吗
Ok?
放松点
Relax.
谢谢
Thank you.
我感谢你
I appreciate it.
- 嗨  宝贝  - 嘿  爸爸  爸爸
-Hi, love. -Hey, dad. Dad?
雷  雷  雷  雷
Ray. Ray? Ray! Ray!
雷  天哪
Ray, jesus christ!
- 都给我趴下  - 雷  求你了
-Everybody down! -Ray, please!
求你了  想想这个
Please. Think about this.
- 想想这个  - 孩子在哪
-Think about this! -Where's the kid?
- 什么  - 雷  雷  雷  雷
-What? -Ray. Ray. Ray. Ray.
不
No!
那孩子在哪
where's the kid?
- 上帝啊  雷  - 你他妈的给我闭嘴
-Jesus christ, ray! -Shut the fuck up.
- 闭嘴  - 求你别这样  雷
- Shut up! - Please don't do this, ray!
- 我想帮你  哪个孩子  - 我再说一遍  伙计
- I wanna help you! Which kid? - One more time, pal.
如果你不把我想知道的事告诉我
You don't tell me what I wanna know, right,
我就让你奶奶的脑浆
I'm gonna spread your granny's brains
都溅到这个该死的地毯上
all over the fuckin' carpet.
- 不要  雷  - 什么孩子
- No, ray! - What kid?
冲我开枪吧
Just shoot me!
- 冲我开枪吧  - 雷
- Shoot me. - Ray!
听着  我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
听着  我真的很抱歉
Look, I'm...I'm sorry.
抱歉我对你说了那些话  我当时太生气了  仅此而已
I'm sorry for what I said. I was angry. That's it.
我哥哥就是个莽夫
My brother was a hothead.
我都知道的  但我很想他
I know. I just miss him.
听听他说的话  求你了  雷  求你了
Listen to what he's saying. Please, ray. Please.
求你了
Please.
天呐
oh, god.
- 什么鬼啊  弗雷迪  - 抱歉  我也不知道会这样
- fucking hell, freddy! - Sorry. I didn't know!
我之前也不知道  你没事吧  亲爱的  我很抱歉
I didn't know. You alright, darling? I'm so sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
加斯：
我现在正在忙
回头再聊
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
- 皮吉  - 嘿
- pidgy. - Hey.
- 你就是加里吧  - 蒂姆
- And you must be gary. - Tim?
是的  进来吧
Yeah. Come on in.
所以说
So.
你们想要多少
How much are you after?
- 你有多少  - 4千克
- How much you got? - Four.
- 4千克  - 但我能弄到更多
- Four? - But I can get heaps more.
好的  是好货吗
Ok. It's good stuff?
他的货一直都很好
oh, the gear's always good.
- 是吗  - 你要试一下吗
- Yeah? - Would you like to try it?
不  不用  皮吉说好就行
No, no. Pidgy vouches.
好的
Ok.
你赢了吗  哥们儿
Are you winning, mate?
- 不  他玩儿得很烂  - 什么
- no, he's shit! - What?
没什么  别在意
Oh, don't worry about it. It's alright.
- 都拿来了  - 是的
- All good? - Yeah.
皮吉  你来装一下  我把钱给他
Pidgy, you wanna do that and I'll get the cash?
- 一万吗  - 一万
- 10? - 10.
一万
10.
我日
Fuck!
所以说  你这儿还有什么
So, um...What else you got?
什么都有
All sorts of shit.
有枪吗
Guns?
- 这边请  - 好的
- Right this way. - Ok.
好了  我这儿有把枪  两千块
Right. I've got this...Shottie for two grand.
是870霰弹枪吗
Oh, yeah. 870?
不赖
Mmm, nice.
这把格洛克手枪我可以四千卖给你
I can do this glock for four.
谁都想有一把这种枪
And everyone wants one of those.
不错
Yeah. Nice.
听着  我现在也不需要这些枪
Yeah, look, I don't need any now,
但知道能从哪儿弄到还是挺好的
but good to know where I can get 'em.
没毛病
Righto.
你要药片吗
can I get you some pills?
不  不用了
Nah, nah. I'm all good.
- 麻醉剂呢  - 不  不用了
- How about some coke? - Nah, mate. Nah.
- 兴奋剂呢  - 也不用了  伙计
- Speed? - Nah. All good, mate.
安非他命呢  镇静剂呢
Uppers? Downers?
不  不用了  老天爷啊
Nah, all good. Bloody hell.
你真是万能商店啊
You're a one-stop shop.
我这儿什么都有  伙计
I've got everything, mate.
那你在这里头放了什么东西呢
What have you got down here, hmm?
厨房洗涤槽吗
Kitchen sinks?
是不是
Hey?
很高兴和你做交易
Well, it was a pleasure doing business with you.
跪到地上
Get on the ground.
什么
what?
你他妈给我跪到地上
Get on the fuckin' ground.
你有毛病吧
What's your problem?
皮吉
pidgy.
把他绑起来  到那边去
Tie him up. Get over there.
快点儿  给我滚到那边去
Move it! Get the fuck over there!
那扇上锁的门的钥匙在哪儿
Where's the key to the door with the lock on it?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
- 别开枪  - 那间玩具屋的钥匙
- don't shoot. - The key to the toy room.
把他绑起来  皮吉
tie him up, pidge.
你特么看什么呢
the fuck you looking at?
麦迪
maddy?
你是麦迪  对吗
You maddy? Yeah?
你知道我是谁吗
You know who I am?
你雷叔叔派我来的
Your uncle ray sent me.
他让我带你回家见你妈妈  好吗
He asked me to take you home to your mum, ok?
你想回家吗
You wanna go home?
想吗  好的  走吧  走吧  来吧
Yeah? Ok. Ok, come on. Let's go. Come on.
来吧  这边走  从这边出去
Come on. Just go this way. Go out this way.
你先在这后面坐着
Just jump in the back here.
好了
There you go.
麦迪  你先在这里等着  好吗
Righto, maddy. You wait here, alright?
我马上就回来  然后我就带你回家见妈妈
I'll be back, and I'll take you back to see your mummy.
好吗  好的
Ok? Alright. Ok.
好了  皮吉
Righto, pidge.
你走吧
Piss off.
起来
Get up.
站起来
Get up!
起来  起来
Get up. Get up.
别逼我  混蛋  走起来
Don't fuckin' push it, cunt. Get up.
快点儿
Move it.
下去  快走
Down. Go.
你他妈站这儿干嘛呢
what the fuck are you doing standing around?
进去  进去  进去
Get in. Get in. Get in.
进去
Get in.
嘿  听着  你知道吗
Hey, listen, just so you know.
我们对她什么都没有做  我们只负责卖人而已
We didn't do anything to her, man. We just sell 'em.
加斯：
我找到她了
在卡梅区
克罗利大路66号
你还好吗  麦迪  没事吧
how you going, maddy? You alright?
亲爱的  谢天谢地
oh, darling! Oh, god.
天呐  亲爱的
oh, my god, darling!
快进去  别在外面冻着
Inside, out of the cold.
- 谢谢  - 不客气
- Thanks. - All good.
你没事吧
Are you ok?
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
看那边
* looka yonder *
一大片黑色乌云要来了
* a big, black cloud come! *
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另招募长期居住海外的CC字幕录制童鞋（有酬劳）
联系QQ：864413459 注明：CC录制
就在那边地平线上
* yonder on the horizon *
停在了那条大河边
* stopped at the mighty river *
大河瞬间干涸
* sucked the damn thing dry *
远处雷声隆隆作响
* distant thunder rumble *
像一头饥饿的野兽般嘶吼着
* rumble, hungry like the beast *
那只野兽来了  它来了
* the beast, it cometh, cometh down *
图珀洛受罚
* tupelo bound *
图珀洛
* tupelo *
* oh, tupelo *
那只野兽来了  它来了
* the beast, it cometh tupelo bound *
当母鸡不再下蛋
* why the hen will lay no egg *
当公鸡不再打鸣
* can't get that cock to crow... *